<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addons>
<addon id="plugin.video.xship" version="2024.12.02" name="[B]xShip[/B]" provider-name="xShip-Team">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests"/>
        <import addon="script.module.six"/>
        <import addon="repository.xship" version="1.5.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" version="5.1.100"/>
        <!-- for remote debug -->
        <import addon="script.module.pydevd" optional="true"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="de_DE">xShip: Das Original</summary>
        <summary lang="en_GB">xShip: The Original</summary>
        <description lang="de">xShip wurde als Video-Addon entwickelt, um Streams verschiedenster Webseiten zu sammeln und anzuzeigen. Der Inhalt von xShip, als auch das Angebot an Webseiten-Inhalten wird von den xShip Entwicklern wieder weiter entwickelt.</description>
        <description lang="en_GB">xShip was developed as a video add-on to collect and display streams from various websites. The content of xShip, as well as the range of website content, is being further developed by the xShip developers.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="de_DE">Mit diesem Video-Addon kannst du auf alle angebotenen Streams verschiedenster deutscher Quellen zugreifen. Dieses Addon ist kein offizieller Teil des Kodi Media Center und wird daher nicht von den offiziellen Support-Kanälen abgedeckt! xShip durchsucht die enthaltenen Webseiten nach Streams und stellt diese in einer Übersicht dar. Der bereitgestellte Inhalt der Webseiten steht in keinem Bezug zu xShip oder den Entwicklern! xShip durchsucht die enthaltenen Webseiten nach Streams und stellt diese in einer Übersicht dar.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">With this video add-on you can access all streams offered by various German sources. This add-on is not an official part of the Kodi Media Center and is therefore not covered by the official support channels! xShip searches the included websites for streams and displays them in an overview. The content provided by the websites has no connection to xShip or the developers! xShip searches the included websites for streams and displays them in an overview.</disclaimer>
        <language>de</language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
        <website>https://tiny.one/xship</website>
        <assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<banner>resources/media/banner.png</banner>
			<clearlogo>resources/media/clearlogo.png</clearlogo>
			<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/media/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.resolveurl" name="ResolveURL Repository" provider-name="gujal" version="1.0.0">
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="ResolveURL Repository">
    <dir>
      <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/addons.xml</info>
      <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
      <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/zips/</datadir>
    </dir>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <description lang="en_GB">ResolveURL and Link Tester</description>
    <license></license>
    <language></language>
    <website></website>
    <news></news>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.xship" name="[B]xShip Repository[/B]" version="1.5.0" provider-name="xShip-Team">
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="xShip Repository">
		<dir minversion="18.9.701" maxversion="21.9.700">
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/watchone/watchone.github.io/repo/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum verify="sha256">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/watchone/watchone.github.io/repo/addons.xml.sha256</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/watchone/watchone.github.io/repo/</datadir>
        </dir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="de_DE">xShip Repository</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">xShip Repository</summary>
		<description lang="de_DE">Dies ist das offizielle xShip Repository.[CR]Bei der Bereitstellung einer neuen xShip Version, wird diese vor der Veröffentlichung auf Funktionalität geprüft. Sollten dennoch Probleme auftreten, benachrichtige bitte das offizielle xShip-Team via Telegram.</description>
		<description lang="de_GB">This is the official xShip repository.[CR]When a new xShip version is released, it is tested for functionality before being released. If you still encounter problems, please notify the official xShip team via Telegram.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Sie können dieses Video Addon gerne verwenden. Der bereitgestellte Inhalt der Webseiten steht in keinem Bezug zu xShip oder den Entwicklern! Weitere Informationen finden Sie auf unserer Github Seite.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">You are welcome to use this video addon. The content provided on the websites has no connection to xShip or the developers! For more information, see our Github page.</disclaimer>
		<language>de en</language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
		<website>https://tiny.one/xship</website>
		<source></source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<banner>resources/banner.png</banner>
			<clearlogo>resources/clearlogo.png</clearlogo>
			<screenshot></screenshot>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.resolveurl" name="ResolveURL" version="5.1.154" provider-name="gujal">
    <requires>
        <!-- <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" /> -->
        <import addon="script.module.six" />
        <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.python.twitch" optional="true" />
        <import addon="plugin.googledrive" optional="true" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="lib/default.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Resolver enlaces a videos de sitios populares para poder reproducirlos en XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="hr_HR">Prilagodi najčešće URL-ove video izvora kako bi radili u XBMC/Kodiju.</summary>
        <summary lang="el_GR">Επίλυση συνδέσμων κοινών εξυπηρετητών σε μορφή βίντεο ικανό για αναπαραγωγή στο XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi, simplify addon development of video plugins requiring multi video hosts.</description>
        <description lang="el_GR">Επίλυση συνδέσμων κοινών εξυπηρετητών σε μορφή βίντεο ικανό για αναπαραγωγή στο XBMC/Kodi, απλοποίηση της ανάπτυξης των προσθέτων που χρησιμοποιούν πολλαπλούς εξυπηρετητές για υλικό βίντεο</description>
        <description lang="hr_HR">Prilagodi najčešće URL-ove video izvora kako bi radili u XBMC/Kodiju, pojednostavnjuje razvoj priključaka za video dodatke koji zahtjevaju višestruke video izvore.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This script only resolves video content from legitimate file lockers without prejudice. If this script is being used by 3rd parties to resolve content that you feel infringes upon your Intellectual Property then please take your complaints to the actual website or developer linking to such content and not here. This script in no way searches for any content whatsoever.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το ανωτέρο σενάριο το μόνο που κάνει είναι να επιλύει οπτικοακουστικό περιεχόμενο από νόμιμες πηγές χωρίς προκατάληψη. Εάν το ανωτέρο σενάριο χρησιμοποιηθεί από τρίτους ώστε να επιλύσει περιεχόμενο το οποίο σας προκαλεί αντίδραση ότι παραβιάζει την πνευματική σας ιδιοκτησία παρακαλώ μεταφέρετε τα παραπονά σας στον ιστότοπο τον οποίο βρίσκεται το εν λόγω περιεχόμενο η τον δημιουργό ο οποίος πραγματοποιεί την σύνδεση και όχι εδω. Το σενάριο αυτό ουδεμία περίπτωση πραγματοποιεί αναζήτηση περιεχομένου.</disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
</addons>
